# Antonio Algaba Osuna

London, E1 5JA • 07831230339 • antonioalgabaosuna@gmail.com

#### **Personal Profile**

I am a proactive professional who always strives to achieve excellence with a high level of order and precision. Due to my experience in different environments and situations, I have become an active problem solver who is quick on the feet to finding the best solution.

With the responsibility that comes with leading a team, I have developed a firm but patient management style. I have an appetite for knowledge and always willing to training and self-development.

## **Employment History**

# Apr 2022 - Present Wilson Vale at Taylor Wessing London

**Concierge Manager** 

Taylor Wessing is an international renowned Law firm which has established itself as an upcoming leader in the field. The firm works with many of the global top 50 brands and also supports start-up companies around the world.

In my current role as Concierge Manager, I act as deputy to the General Manager and also provide support to the Hospitality and Events Manager. My role requires flexibility and efficiency in order to cover multiple roles when necessary and meet the needs of the departments.

My current role includes;

- Building solid, professional relationships with all clients and key stakeholders by being approachable, flexible and attentive in fulfilling customer needs.
- Reception duties and being the first point of contact for the client.
- Regularly monitor customer feedback and produce suitable action plans based on the results.
- Support the General Manager in co-ordinating and managing the recruitment and selection process.
- Support all staff in teams linked to service delivery; improve communication and cohesive work across the departments, facilitate and lead team meetings. Induct and monitor performance of new staff.
- Monitor stock and budget, in support of the company's wider financial targets.
- Weekly planning with the Executive Chef regarding client profiles and manage events (fine dining, canapes), when required.
- Improve insights regarding service provision; including developing new systems for capturing and comparing weekly statistics by incorporating diagrams and formulas for excel documents.

# Oct 2019 - May 2022 Gibson, Dunn and Crutcher LLP Catering and Hospitality coordinator-London

Gibson, Dunn & Crutcher LLP, is a leading international law firm which consistently ranks among the world's top law firms in industry surveys and major publications. My role as a catering and hospitality coordinator gave me the ability to manager and develop a team. During the covid pandemic I covered the reception, learning another skill to add to my list.

- Cover reception.
- Coordinating all hospitality food and beverage requests offered to customer.
- Preparing hospitality rooms for visitors.
- Ordering and stocking supplies.
- Supervising helpers in hospitality and coffee shop.
- Administering funds for ordering of supplies.

## Sep 2018 - Oct 19 Baxterstorey at Addleshaw Goddard LLP

**Hospitality assistant - London** 

Addleshaw Goddard is a law firm known worldwide for their innovation in the industry with a keen interest in promoting a holistic approach. I assisted the hospitality manager in ordering stock and budget sheets. This required me to learn good organizational skills to monitor stock control.

- Prepare all hospitality food and beverage requests offered to customers.
- Setting up the meeting rooms layout.
- Ensure hospitality rooms are left tidy.
- Control stock and reduce waste.
- Promote good team work and work in a friendly, efficient manner.
- Ensure the safety and security of company and client property.
- Comply with all Company and Client policies and procedures, statutory regulations relating to the work place, this includes but not limited to fire; health and safety; hygiene; working safely; CoSHH.

## Apr 2016 - Sep 2018 Compass Group at KPMG

## **Customer Services Assistant – London**

KPMG is a multinational services network, and one of the Big Four accounting organizations in the world. Having high standards for their field, they expected us to be professional and efficient at our job. We provided a warm space for customers to come to while giving them a positive experience.

- Ensure food hygiene and health and safety regulations are always adhered to
- · Preparation and cleaning of the restaurant area
- The serving of meals ensuring correct portion control
- Giving information and helping to solve customer problems
- Answering customer enquiries or passing them on to the appropriate department
- Answered department telephone calls.
- Assisted colleagues whenever possible.
- Assisted in cashiering and Point of Sale system procedures during busy hours.

#### **Qualifications**

- Environmental Management course (ISO 14001). University of Exeter. United Kingdom.
- Master in Integrated Quality, Environmental and Health and Safety Management System. San Pablo's University, Spain.
- Bachelor's Degree in Biology. University of Cordoba, Spain.

### **Skills and Competences**

- Critical thinking
- Attention to detail
- Adaptability and responsiveness
- Quick learner
- Effective time management
- Positive learning environment
- Computer proficient
- Customer services
- Knowledge of ISO 9001 and 14001
- Spanish speaker (native)